<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>kde and vic</title>
    <link>http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/</link>
    <description>Recent content on kde and vic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 19:25:58 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week2</title>
      <link>http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/posts/week2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 19:25:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/posts/week2/</guid>
      <description>Combing through KDE&amp;rsquo;s sites to check for compliance with WCAG A-level KDE&amp;rsquo;s Main Site Assistive Reader No issues.
Alternative Text on Images With KDE Eco:
&amp;lt;img class=&amp;#34;img-fluid&amp;#34; src=&amp;#34;https://kde.org/images/eco_greenerywithlogo_box_500.jpg&amp;#34; alt=&amp;#34;&amp;#34; width=&amp;#34;500&amp;#34; loading=&amp;#34;lazy&amp;#34;&amp;gt; ... &amp;lt;img alt=&amp;#34;BMUV&amp;#34; src=&amp;#34;https://eco.kde.org//assets/img/bmuv.webp&amp;#34;&amp;gt; BMUV is not very descriptive.
KDE Plasma Assistive Reader No issues.
Alternative Text on Images All images had alternative text.
ETC No other issues found.
Krita Assistive Reader No issues.
Alternative Text on Images &amp;lt;img class=&amp;#34;lazy loaded&amp;#34; src=&amp;#34;https://krita.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WCAG</title>
      <link>http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/posts/wcag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:26:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/posts/wcag/</guid>
      <description>Reading the WCAG &amp;amp; Taking More In-Depth Notes Page 13: Controls, Input If non-text content is a control or accepts user input, then it must have a name to describe its purpose (i.e., sign up for mailing lists, etc) – refer to success criterion 4.1.2 Decoration, Formatting, Invisible: NON text content that’s pure decoration should be formatted so that it can be ignored by assistive technology (likely, do a comb through of existing KDE sites with text-to-speech readers)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week1</title>
      <link>http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/posts/week1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 16:37:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/posts/week1/</guid>
      <description>Start of SoK Hello! Today (in UTC) marks the official start of Season of KDE! In about two weeks or so, I&amp;rsquo;ll update the site on what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned, but recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading up on web accessibility guidelines according to those latest published by WCAG.
WCAG During my research, I noted the following that could be applicable to KDE&amp;rsquo;s main sites, with the following in quotes either paraphrased or taken directly from WCAG 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre Season of KDE - Hugo &amp; Setting Goals</title>
      <link>http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/posts/hugo--setting-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 23:35:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/posts/hugo--setting-goals/</guid>
      <description>I had never heard of KDE prior to learning about Season of KDE, but I had actually used one of their developed softwares before even knowing it was associated with KDE - Krita. I started this blog in interest of Season of KDE, but I hope to start to contribute to OSS like KDE even outside of SoK. :)
Setting Up &amp;amp; Learning Hugo KDE uses Hugo to template a lot of their subdomains, so I figured it would be relevant to learn to help improve accessability &amp;amp; overall function across their different sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First!</title>
      <link>http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/posts/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 21:51:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://victoriaemily.github.io/KDE/posts/first/</guid>
      <description>This is the first test blog post! I have added a comments section &amp;amp; familiarized myself a little with Hugo. Goals for now:
create a comment system using mongo atlas create a mockup of a KDE site create my first detailed post at the end detailing what i&amp;rsquo;ve done today! Thanks for reading this test blog post. :) </description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
